{
    "id": "0eacd6a6a40141568100e58d7d1064fc",
    "title": "Make meaningful sentences",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "7676cda10eb04c9193ef1a5b5ca8f7d2",
            "title": "Make Meaningful Sentences",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She ................................. a story.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is reading",
                        "are reading",
                        "has reading"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The child ........................................ for his father.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wait",
                        "is waiting",
                        "has waiting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who ................................... at the gate?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is standing",
                        "stand",
                        "stands"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ........................................ less butter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "am eating",
                        "are eating",
                        "have eating"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My grandmother .......................................... past slowly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was walking",
                        "were walking",
                        "have walking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "David ......................................... across a field one sunny morning.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has strolling",
                        "was strolling",
                        "are strolling"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "A pair of trousers ....................................... in the cupboard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "are hanging",
                        "is hanging"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sharon ..................................... from a cold.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has suffering",
                        "is suffering",
                        "were suffering"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He .................................. his lessons.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is learning",
                        "has learning",
                        "learn"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That child ................................. bigger everyday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is getting",
                        "get",
                        "has getting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}